

ROBERT DEVINE IT SCIENTIST ENGINEER









EDUCATION

Chemistry & Physics

Villanova University
B.Sc, <u>SPS AIP</u> Honor Society

Engineering Science

Penn State University
Data Architecture, Patterns

Regulatory Compliance

Duke University Med School

CDER, CBER, CDRH

FDA Badges: R Clinical Reporting, Drug Discovery - Graph Neural Network

SKILLS

LANGUAGES SKILLS

R/Python/Julia/Haskell/C++

DevOps [Git | Kubernetes]

SCIENTIFIC SKILLS

HPLC

Waters Empower, Alliance

Laboratory Software, DBA

INTERPERSONAL SKILLS

Work under Pressure

Analytical Skills

Communication/Leadership

Multi-tasking

PROFILE

Robert Devine is a Scientist and an Engineer deeply committed to the advancement of research in medicine. He is highly-experienced with engineering design patterns related to quality and scientific laboratory R&D in diverse settings from manufacturing industry to pharmaceuticals to the military.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Brand Owner, R&D Scientist

2022-Present

SmartGxP™, Villanova, PA, United States

Manufacturing R&D Laboratory Quality

- Net Total Care (SNTC) Portal and Common Service Platform Collector (CSPC).
- Responsible for customers consistently and surpassing goals quarter over quarter, utilizing Salesforce to track and communicate including Box.
- Focused on Customer Experience and Customer
 Success with advanced understanding of the Cisco and SAP portfolio, offers and teams.
- Updated and managed the Deployment Playbook to ensure Internal information is up-to-date.

Drive vision and commercialization of the SmartGxPTM brand. Inspire colleagues about *Quality*, *Regulatory Compliance*, *Formal Methods*, and *Automation*

System Administrator / Manager

2022-2024

Manufacturing Logistics and Laboratory, Spring House, PA J&J/Janssen Deployed Intelligent Automation Solutions

- Automated Quotes to Support Lab Infrastructure
- Quality Framework Delivery GxP Change Mgmt.
- Focus on Customer Experience and Customer Success developing Productivity Toolsets

Ensured full compliance with JJT (Johnson & Johnson Technology) policies regarding SCM (Software Configuration Management) and Extensible Networked Laboratory Applications at Enterprise Scale



ROBERT DEVINE IT SCIENTIST ENGINEER









HOBBIES

Reading

Travel





Health

Antiques





VOLUNTEERING

January 2014 - Present

American Institute of Physics, Serve as a Mentor

January 2021 - Present

R Consortium Working Group,

Serve as an Author and Contributor

March 2022 - Present

AAPS Screener

Pharmaceutical Sciences

Serve as Screener for Paper/Posters Abstracts

October 2022 - Present

J&J HHS-TAP Awareness

New Jersey High Schools

Serve as SME for J&J

RECOGNITION

United States Navy Total Quality Honoree [TQM]

Statistical Process Controls in Mfg.

Gran Prix Level Dressage Owner

Animal Rights Advocate

Fortune 500 Technology Educator

United States Air Force

Phase I-III SBIR Awards
-Complex Chalcogenide Tribology
Staff Scientist Role

CONTINUED WORK EXPERIENCE

Enterprise Architect

2014-2023

Xyntek [CXV Global], Inc., Newtown, PA, United States
On-boarded Global CRO/CDMO vendors for J&J/Janssen

- Originated highly-specialized Big Data | Unified Analytics Platform for Integrated Data Management
- Data Responsibility for 300+ scientists consistently.
- Integrated Data Management Data Architect, JJT
 SCM Platform Team Scientific Expert Data Science and Formal Methods, Semantic Ontology

Ensured full compliance with JJT (Johnson & Johnson Technology) policies regarding SCM (Software Configuration Management)

DevOps Skills

- Kubernetes Full Stack Automation
- Greenfield Tanzu 2.x Kubernetes on AWS
- Unix/Linux administration
- Terraform and ARM Infrastructure Management
- Automation server (Jenkins JPM, GitLab)
- Manage full-lifecycle automation (SCM DevOps, Security)
- Cloud-based servers (AWS, Azure, GCP)
- Big Data Engines (Hadoop, Kafka, Spark, Impala)
- Apache Web Server, Nginx
- Continuous Integration and Continuous Delivery
 - (CI/CD) across Git long-life branches
- Programming languages
- .NET, Java, Python, Go, C++, Haskell, Bash, R, Julia, LINQ
- Enterprise Service Integration (Jira, ServiceNow)
- Microservices (Technical Debt, Governance, API)
- Agile methodology (Scrum, Kanban)
- AWS Controllers for Kubernetes [ACK]
- Zero-Trust Networks [ZTNA]
- Terraform Module Validation
- External Data Management of CRO/CDMO Vendors
- Intelligent Automation



ROBERT DEVINE IT SCIENTIST ENGINEER









TO:

SmartGxP[™] Colleagues January 27, 2024

Dear Colleagues and Visitors

Thank you for taking time from your day to browse the SmartGxPTM brochure. If you have any questions please reach out through any of the digital contact points listed above. We offer highest-quality GxP laboratory services at value-added cost including flexible electronic-billing for short-term work orders involving both laboratory and manufacturing automation which can be as short as one hour of billed engagement to deliver best-in-class automation. We offer expert-level systematic testing and validation services to deliver distinguished product quality and support.

Our extensive experience delivering quality drives key performance indicators and efficiency to realize targeted performance goals demanded by the industry. Please engage with us today to gain insight about how our services and team can assist you to drive further value for your products, supply chains, and customers. Thank you again!

Sincerely,

Robert Devine

Robert Devine